S. NAJUA SAAD

SKILLS

I have years of versatile experience serving, bartending, and managing restaurants where I gained useful experience working in team settings. I'm motivated, punctual, and hard-working. I'm great at anticipating clients' needs, maintaining a good attitude, work ethic, and demeanor.

I'm currently in the middle of an intense coding bootcamp at the University of Minnesota. While I'm new to web development, I have years of relevant work experience working in team settings, problem solving, and working directly with clients and suppliers.

EDUCATION

University of Minnesota Coding Bootcamp, Minneapolis, MN

MARCH 2021 - MAY 2021

An intense, full stack program that teaches HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, node.js, and more. The class includes at least two homework assignments a week and is designed not only to teach code writing and logic, but also to prepare us for working in the field with three large group projects.

TECHNOLOGIES

HTML/CSS, Git, Bootstrap, Javascript, JQuery, APIs, AJAX, Node, Express Servers, MySQL, Handlebars, Sequelize, Testing, Error Handling, Heroku, MongoDB, PWAs, React, MERN, and Computer Science

WORK EXPERIENCE

Barrel Theory Beer Company, St. Paul, MN

Hospitality Coordinator/Lead Bartender

APRIL 2017 - JANUARY 2020

I helped open Barrel Theory in June 2017. I started by stocking the bar, hand washing glasses, moving kegs, tending the bar, and occasionally doing production work. I was promoted to Lead Bartender and Hospitality Coordinator as the company expanded. I was in charge of the merch, our relationship with our printing company, inventory, and promotion as well as everything between turning my key and shutting off the alarm in the morning to making deposits in the safe before locking up at night.

Surly Brewing Company, Minneapolis MN

Server Captain

MARCH 2016 - AUGUST 2017

High volume restaurant with quality food and ingredients on a rotating menu. My responsibilities as a captain included guiding my co-workers on the floor, handling comps and voids when managers weren't around, and ensuring all the closing server side work for up to eighteen servers was completed. I occasionally bartended the busy outside bar, as well

R. Thomas, Atlanta GA

Server/Manager

2011 - 2015

This 24-hour restaurant handles high volume, rowdy crowds at night and busy breakfasts and brunches. As a server, I worked third shift for the first couple years I was there before moving my schedule to mostly work dinners. I typically worked volume shifts that entailed being the only server on the floor as well as working the gravity bar and some minor kitchen detail before the rest of the crew would arrive. As a manager, I handled the store bank, inventory, ordering, fixing immediate maintenance issues, and customers. This job required patience and a sense of humor all while maintaining a professional attitude and sense of urgency.